

Contacts

+380-093-594-1984

sirov@ukr.net

<u>Telegram</u>

GitHub

Linkedin

Nosivka, Ukraine

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- SASS
- BEM
- React
- Redux
- REST API
- Laravel
- npm
- MySQL
- PHP

Soft Skills

- Critical thinking
- Time management
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Creativity

Languages

- Ukrainian native
- Russian upper-intermediate
- English intermediate

Oleh Syrovatko

Junior Front-End Developer

Summary

With over 10 years of experience as a full-stack developer, including working on a large-scale social ped project, I am excited to pursue a role as a Junior Front-End Developer. I have successfully contributed to the creation of a popular social network for Ukrainian settlements, which attracted 583K unique visitors in 2022. I am confident that my skills, passion and experience in building user-centric applications will enable me to make valuable contributions to your company.

Project Experience

lua.com.ua (HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL)

First social network about all Ukrainian settlements. Contain more than 1 million photos and 115k users organized by Laravel Framework. Role: Team lead. Individual project.

WebStudio, GitHub (HTML, SASS)

It's a little portfolio about some IT company. Several pages introduse goals, productrs, spesialists, clients and company contacts. Role: Developer. Individual project.

MIMIHO, GitHub (HTML, SASS, JS, Parce)

It's a small project about restaurant. All the pages mobile adapted, have excelent performance, accessibility.

Role: Team lead. Group project.

<u>Phonebook, GitHub</u> (React: Hooks, Router, Redux)

A simple phonebook connected to backend API - you can register, log in, add, remove or filter contacts, log out.

Role: Developer. Individual project

Work Experience

Chief Accountant

PE Sa-Ha Trans 2016-present

- Accounting: Financial record-keeping and compliance
- International Logistics: Managing global shipments and deliveries
- Finance: Financial operations oversight and analysis

Achieving an increase in the company's profitability and an increase in its capital more than 30%.

Full Stack Developer

First allukrainian social network 2006-present

- full development lifecycle, including concept-to-deployment
- ensuring best practices and quality standards
- · conducting code reviews, provide code quality and maintainability
- implementing scalable database structures
- handling large volumes of photos and user data

Achievement: 583K unique visitors per 2022 year.

Education

2022 – 2023 IT School GoIT, Fullstack Developer

2000 – 2005 Kyiv National Economic University, Master of accounting,

analysis and auditing